

## Tetiana Kelly

Web Full Stack Engineer

O San Francisco, CA

#### Profile

Software engineer with 3 years of professional experience. My journey started from a simple script I wrote to automate manual workflows for my team and became my true passion. Today I build full stack web applications in different environments, work with relational and non-relational databases, and work on beautiful UI.

Big reader and dreamer, meditator and yogi, climber, former Ukrainian tv-journalist and immigrant, I believe that technologies make this world better place and I want to be a part of it.

## **Employment History**

#### 1/2019 to Present

## Full Stack Software Engineer at ElmTree System

ElmTree System is a laboratory information management software (LIMS) developed for construction materials testing laboratories.

- Built ElmTree's new client onboarding tool. This desktop
  web application is used to speed up new laboratory
  onboarding and simplify client form customizations.
  Designed and implemented key features including user
  authentication, visual representation of form settings, and
  dynamic add/edit/delete functionality. Created MS SQL db
  queries and wrapped them in API calls for the frontend.
  Built the frontend with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery,
  AJAX, React and Bootstrap.
- Worked on new feature development for ElmTree's Field Technical Rep application. This is a mobile web application used by laboratories to manage their mobile workforce. Functionality includes job assignments, data collection and processing, workflow management and time tracking. Collaborated with principle engineers to develop APIs, modify database structure and write SQL queries. Architected flexible dynamically generated UI for technical forms with different level of complexity.

#### 2/2017 - 8/2018

# Software Engineer in Test, Automation Engineer at GridNet

Internet of Things and Smart Grid software company, whose smart electric/water meters are used by multiple utilities in different countries.

- Created a test automation framework with Python, Selenium, and Unix for continuous validation of device reporting data and subscribe/unsubscribe functionality.
- Managed test plans and created new test cases for ongoing feature development and bug fixes.
- Managed and developed automated API testing with SOAPUI tools.

#### **Details**

+1 (415) 794-4881

murenkot@gmail.com

**GitHub** 

Portfolio Portfolio

(in) LinkenIn

### Skills

- JavaScript
- Python
- PHP
- HTML
- CSS
- Node.js
- React.js
- Ajax
- jQuery
- Django
- Selenium
- Bootstrap
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB Git
- GitHub

#### 11/2016 - 5/2018

## Data Engineer, Automation Engineer at Boys and Girls Clubs of San Francisco

Boys & Girls Clubs of America (BGCA) is a national organization of local chapters which provide after-school programs for young people.

- Designed automation scripts using Python and Selenium Webdriver to update and clean database.
- Analyzed/validated large data sets using Python scripts.
- Built data pipelines with Python and SQL to create a variety of datasets for the Outcome Measurements Team. Wrote SQL queries as a part of data pipelines for consistent monitoring of data quality.

#### Education

#### 2018

#### San Francisco

## General Assembly

Top graduate of GA's 'Software Engineering Immersive' bootcamp. A full-time, classroom based course covering full-stack web based development. Built 5 full-stack web applications on diverse teams of developers and UI/UX designers:

- Local social network for dog owners (Dogborhood) with Node on the backend and React + Google Maps JS API on the frontend.
- · Full-featured travel blog with Node and React.
- Time tracking app with Node.js, MongoDB and JavaScript.
- Space poetry blog leveraging Python, PostgreSQL, the Django MVC framework, and NASA's imagery API.
- · Web-based game with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

#### 2007

Kyiv, Ukraine

## Kyiv National University of Technology and Design

BA, Economics